Stanley Woodward
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Stanley Woodward papers
1875-1970, bulk 1905-1970
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
Woodward, Stanley
6.6 linear feet
The papers of marine painter, illustrator, writer and art instructor Stanley Woodward date from 1875-1970, bulk 1905-1970, and measure 6.6 linear feet. Found within the papers are biographical materials, family and personal correspondence, seventeen diaries, notes, notebooks and other writings, business records, a scrapbook and printed material including exhibition announcements and catalogs; and photographs of Woodward, members of his family, friends, his studio, and artwork. Files containing letters, clippings, and photographs concern actresses including Janis Carter, Linda Darnell, Bette Davis, and Eleanor Powell. Writings include drafts of Woodward's book Adventure in Marine Painting.
Provenance
The Stanley Woodward papers were donated in two installments in 1973 by Stanley Woodward's daughter, Patricia Woodward Smith.
Restrictions on Access
The collection is open for research. Use requires an appointment.
Biographical Note
Stanley Wingate Woodward was born on December 11, 1890, in Malden, Massachusetts, son of Alice E. (Colesworthy) and Frank E. Woodward. He was one of eight children and a twin of Sidney, who later became an art dealer and critic.
In 1909, Woodward graduated from Malden High School and the family moved to Wellesley Hills. He studied at the Eric Pape School of Art, the School of the Boston Museum of Fine Arts, and the Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts. He left school to serve in France as a Corporal in the Field Artillery 28th Division during World War I. After the war, he settled in Ogunquit, Maine, and became a free lance illustrator for Collier's and the Christian Science Monitor, where his brother Sidney was art editor.
In 1925, he held his first solo show of marine oils at Casson Galleries, Boston, where his twin brother Sidney was manager. He was encouraged to continue painting the ocean after the entire exhibition sold out.
Woodward married Ruth Brainerd in 1926 and they settled in Newton, Massachusetts, where they were neighbors to a young Bette Davis, who had recently graduated from high school. Woodward maintained contact with the actress for the rest of his life, and through Ms. Davis, he befriended other show business personalities.
During the 1930s, Woodward taught painting at the Woodward Outdoor Painting School of Rockport, Massachusetts, at the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, at the Ringling School of Art in Sarasota, Florida, and at the Laguna Beach School in California. In 1937, he established his residence and studio in Rockport, Massachusetts.
Woodward served as an Air Corps captain and director of camouflage training at McChord Field in Tacoma, Washington, during World War II. In 1947, he published a book on painting techniques entitled Adventure in Marine Painting. He was also the author of Marine Paintings in Oil and Water Color.
Woodward was a member of the Chicago Society of Etchers, the Concord Art Association, the Print Makers Society of California, the Boston Society of Water Color Painters, Allied Artists of America, the Guild of Boston Artists, the North Shore Art Association, the American Water Color Society, the Grand Central Galleries Association, and the Rockport Art Association. His work is in the collections of the Boston Museum of Fine Arts, Bowdoin College, Amherst College, Lehigh University, and the Prudential Life Insurance Collection.
Stanley Wingate Woodward died on March 21, 1970 in Gloucester, Massachusetts.
Scope and Content Note
The papers of marine painter, illustrator, writer and art instructor Stanley Woodward date from 1875-1970, bulk 1905-1970, and measure 6.6 linear feet. Found within the papers are biographical materials, artworks, family and personal correspondence, seventeen diaries, notes, notebooks and other writings, business records, a scrapbook and printed material including exhibition announcements and catalogs; and photographs of Woodward, members of his family, friends, and his studio. Files containing letters, clippings, and photographs concern actresses including Janis Carter, Linda Darnell, Bette Davis, and Eleanor Powell. Writings include drafts of Woodward's book Adventure in Marine Painting.
Biographical material includes miscellaneous accounts of Woodward's life, cards and certificates of membership in various organizations including the Massachusetts Society of the Sons of the American Revolution, the Salmagundi Club, and the Academic Artist Association, military records of his service in both World Wars, and scattered artwork. A file concerning Woodward's portrait of Abraham Lincoln contains letters primarily discussing a reproduction of the portrait in The Boston Globe and the painting's eventual sale, in addition to notes, clippings, an ink drawing, and a photographic negative of the drawing.
Correspondence is between various family members, but also includes letters to Woodward from colleagues including Harrison Cady, Eleanor Parke Custis, Ralph Fabri, Chauncey F. Ryder, and Howard E. Smith. There are also scattered letters from other artists including Gifford Beal, Mary Butler, Gordon Grant, Norman Kent, Hobart Nichols, Thornton Oakley, Edmund Tarbell, and Anthony Thieme. Correspondence primarily concern his painting career, and includes lists of art work and financial material.
Artwork consists of a sketchbook and three sketches.
Files concerning actresses reflect Woodward's life-long friendship with former teenaged neighbor Bette Davis, who later introduced Woodward and his art work to her show business friends. The files contain letters, clippings, and photographs of actresses Janis Carter, Linda Darnell, Bette Davis, Laraine Day, Madaline Lee, Ida Lupino, Eleanor Powell, and Alexis Smith.
Seventeen diaries contain relatively detailed daily entries describing Woodward's art-related activities, experiences during World War II, and various travels, including a trip to Los Angeles to be a house guest of Bette Davis and visit her on the set of the motion picture Elizabeth and Essex. The 1905 diary contains photographs of Woodward's school friends.
Notes, notebooks, and writings include lists of art works, exhibition guest books, and miscellaneous writings by Woodward including drafts of his book Adventure in Marine Painting.
Business records include an auction catalog, account books for the sale of Woodward's book and art work, and miscellaneous receipts. Records of art classes taught by Woodward include lists of participants, accounts of fees paid, and printed advertisements.
A scrapbook containing clippings and exhibition announcements and catalogs illustrates Woodward's early interests and art-related activities.
Additional printed material consists of clippings, copies of the U. S. Air Corps Magazine The Rip Chord for which Woodward did the cover illustrations, prospectuses with annotations of titles and prices of art work, exhibition announcements and catalogs, reproductions of art work, a booklet, and brochures for books and for art schools. Miscellaneous printed material includes reproductions of a photograph of Woodward's father, Frank E. Woodward, and a program for an event honoring Dr. T. Tertius Noble.
Photographs are of Woodward, family members, friends connected with the U. S. Army Air Force including Jack Dempsey, Woodward's studio, and art work. Three albums contain photographs of art classes and Woodward painting outdoors at various locations including Laguna Beach and Palm Springs, California, St. Augustine, Florida, and Rockport, Massachusetts. A third album also contains photographs of notable friends including Janis Carter, Jeanne Craine, Bette Davis, Rita Hayworth, and Gary Merrill.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into 10 series. Each series is arranged chronologically.
Series 1: Biographical Material, 1918-1968 (Boxes 1, 8; 15 folders)
Series 2: Artwork, circa 1920s (Boxes 1; 2 folders)
Series 3: Correspondence, 1910-1969 (Boxes 1-3; 2.9 linear feet)
Series 4: Files Concerning Actresses, 1931-1970 (Boxes 4, 8; 0.75 linear feet)
Series 5: Diaries, 1905-1969 (Boxes 4-5; 10 folders)
Series 6: Notes, Notebooks, and Writings, 1915-1969 (Boxes 5, 8; 21 folders)
Series 7: Business Records, 1924-1969 (Boxes 5-6; 15 folders)
Series 8: Scrapbook, 1875-1919 (Box 6; 1 folder)
Series 9: Printed Material, 1916-1970 (Boxes 6-7; 0.75 linear feet)
Series 10: Photographs, 1920-1969 (Boxes 7-8, OV 9; 11 folders)
Names and Subject Terms
This collection is indexed in the online catalog of the Archives of American Art under the following terms:
Subjects:
Carter, Janis, 1921-; Craine, Jeanne; Darnell, Linda, 1921-1965; Davis, Bette, 1908-1989; Hayworth, Rita, 1918-1987; Merrill, Gary; Powell, Eleanor, 1912-1982; Salmagundi Sketch Club
Subjects-Topical:
Marine painting -- Technique; Illustrators -- Massachusetts; Marine painters -- Massachusetts; Educators -- Massachusetts; World War, 1914-1918; World War, 1939-1945; Artists' studios
Types of Materials:
Diaries; Writings; Scrapbooks; Photographs; Drawings
Names:
Beal, Gifford, 1879-1956; Butler, Mary; Cady, Harrison, 1877-1970; Custis, Eleanor Parke, 1897-1983; Davis, Bette, 1908-1989; Day, Laraine, 1920-2007; Fabri, Ralph, 1894-; Grant, Gordon, 1875-1962; Kent, Norman, 1903-1972; Lee, Madaline; Lupino, Ida, 1918-1995; Nichols, Hobart, 1869-1962; Oakley, Thornton, 1881-1953; Ryder, Chauncey F., 1868-1949; Smith, Alexis, 1921-1993; Smith, Howard --(Howard Everett), 1885-1970; Tarbell, Edmund Charles, 1862-1938; Thieme, Anthony, 1888-1954
Series Descriptions/Container Listing
- Biographical Material, 1918-1968, Series 1:; (Boxes 1, 8; 15 folders)
  Biographical material includes miscellaneous accounts of Woodward's life, cards and certificates of membership in various organizations including the Massachusetts Society of the Sons of the American Revolution, the Salmagundi Club, and the Academic Artist Association, and military records of his service in both World Wars. Files concerning Woodward's portrait of Abraham Lincoln contain letters primarily discussing a reproduction of the portrait in The Boston Globe and the painting's eventual sale, notes, clippings, an ink drawing, and a photographic negative of the drawing.
  - Biographical Accounts, 1941-1960, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Membership Cards and Certificates, 1918-1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Military Records, 1918-1945, (4 folders) (Box 1, Folder 3-6)
  - File Concerning Woodward's Portrait of Abraham Lincoln, 1956-1965, (6 folders; see also Box 8 for oversized) (Box 1, Folder 7-12)
  - Oversized Ink Drawing of Portrait of Abraham Lincoln, undated (Box 8 (sol))
- Artwork, circa 1920s, Series 2:; (Box 1; 2 folders)
  Artwork consists of one sketchbook of pencil drawings and three loose sketches. The loose sketches include a cityscape of Amesterdam; a home in Santa Barbara, California; and a watercolor of Key West, Florida.
  - Sketchbook, circa 1920s (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Sketches, circa 1920s (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1910-1969, Series 3:; (Boxes 1-3; 2.9 linear feet)
  This series consists of correspondence between family members and letters to Woodward primarily concerning his painting career including some lists of art work and some financial material. Correspondents include Harrison Cady, Eleanor Parke Custis, Ralph Fabri, Chauncey F. Ryder, and Howard E. Smith. There are scattered letters from other artists including Gifford Beal, Mary Butler, Gordon Grant, Norman Kent, Hobart Nichols, Thornton Oakley, Edmund Tarbell, and Anthony Thieme.
  - Family Correspondence between Stanley and Ruth Woodward, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Family Correspondence from Pat Woodward, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence between Miscellaneous Family Members, 1936-1938 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence between Miscellaneous Family Members, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence between Miscellaneous Family Members, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence between Miscellaneous Family Members, 1943, (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
  - Correspondence between Miscellaneous Family Members, 1944, (6 folders) (Box 1, Folder 22-27)
  - Correspondence between Miscellaneous Family Members, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence between Miscellaneous Family Members, 1949-1953 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Unknown Surnames, undated, (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 30-31)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Surnames "A-B," undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Surnames "C-F," undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Surnames "G-K," undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Surnames "L-N," undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Surnames "O-R," undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Surnames "S-T," undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Letters from Correspondents with Surnames "U-Z," undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Letters from Harrison Cady, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Letters from Chauncey F. Ryder, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Letters, 1910-1919 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Letters, 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Letters, 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Letters, 1925-1927 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Letters, 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Letters, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Letters, 1932, (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 47-48)
  - Letters, 1933, (3 folders) (Box 1, Folder 49-51)
  - Letters, 1934, (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 52-53)
  - Letters, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Letters, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Letters, 1937, (8 folders) (Box 1, Folder 56-63)
  - Letters, 1938, (8 folders) (Box 1, Folder 64-71)
  - Letters, 1939, (6 folders) (Box 1, Folder 72-77)
  - Letters, 1940, (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 78-79)
  - Letters, 1941, (10 folders) (Box 1, Folder 80-89)
  - Letters, 1942, (6 folders) (Box 2, Folder 1-6)
  - Letters, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Letters, 1944, (4 folders) (Box 2, Folder 8-11)
  - Letters, 1945, (8 folders) (Box 2, Folder 12-19)
  - Letters, 1946, (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 20-22)
  - Letters, 1947, (4 folders) (Box 2, Folder 23-26)
  - Letters, 1948, (5 folders) (Box 2, Folder 27-31)
  - Letters, 1949, (5 folders) (Box 2, Folder 32-36)
  - Letters, 1950, (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 37-38)
  - Letters, 1951, (4 folders) (Box 2, Folder 39-42)
  - Letters, 1952, (6 folders) (Box 2, Folder 43-48)
  - Letters, 1953, (9 folders) (Box 2, Folder 49-57)
  - Letters, 1954, (9 folders) (Box 2, Folder 58-66)
  - Letters, 1955, (8 folders) (Box 2, Folder 67-74)
  - Letters, 1956, (6 folders) (Box 3, Folder 1-6)
  - Letters, 1957, (8 folders) (Box 3, Folder 7-14)
  - Letters, 1958, (7 folders) (Box 3, Folder 15-21)
  - Letters, 1959, (8 folders) (Box 3, Folder 22-29)
  - Letters, 1960, (3 folders) (Box 3, Folder 30-32)
  - Letters, 1961 (7 folders) (Box 3, Folder 33-39)
  - Letters, 1962 (8 folders) (Box 3, Folder 40-47)
  - Letters, 1963 (7 folders) (Box 3, Folder 48-54)
  - Letters, 1964 (3 folders) (Box 3, Folder 55-57)
  - Letters, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Letters, 1966 (5 folders) (Box 3, Folder 59-63)
  - Letters, 1967 (8 folders) (Box 3, Folder 64-71)
  - Letters, 1968 (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 72-73)
  - Letters, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Files Concerning Actresses, 1931-1970, Series 4:; (Boxes 4, 8; 0.75 linear feet)
  These files contain letters, clippings, and photographs of actresses Janis Carter, Linda Darnell, Bette Davis, Laraine Day, Madaline Lee, Ida Lupino, Eleanor Powell, and Alexis Smith. A neighbor of teen-aged Bette Davis, Woodward maintained contact with her for the rest of his life. Through Ms. Davis, Woodward also befriended other show business personalities.
  - Letters from Janis Carter, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Letters from Janis Carter, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Letters from Janis Carter, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Letters from Janis Carter, 1950, (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 4-5)
  - Letters from Janis Carter, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Letters from Janis Carter, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Letters from Janis Carter, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Letters from Janis Carter, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Letters from Janis Carter, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Letters from Janis Carter, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Letters from Janis Carter, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Letters from Janis Carter, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Letters from Janis Carter, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Letters from Janis Carter, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Letters from Janis Carter, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Letters from Janis Carter, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Letters from Janis Carter, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Letters from Janis Carter, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Clippings and Photographs of Janis Carter, 1941-1961 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Letters from Linda Darnell, 1952-1957 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Letters from Linda Darnell, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Letters from Linda Darnell, 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Photographs of Linda Darnell with Woodward, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Letters from Bette Davis, 1943-1953, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Clippings about Bette Davis, 1931-1970, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Letters from Laraine Day and Clipping about Laraine Day, 1963-1968, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Letters from Madaline Lee (Radio Actress), 1941-1942, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Autographed Picture Postcard from Ida Lupino, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Letters from Eleanor Powell, 1962-1963, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Letters from Eleanor Powell, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Letters from Eleanor Powell, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Letters from Alexis Smith, 1946-1950 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Oversized Autographed Photograph of Bette Davis, undated (Box 8 (sol))
- Diaries, 1905-1969, Series 5:; (Boxes 4-5; 10 folders)
  Seventeen diaries contain relatively detailed daily entries describing Woodward's art-related activities, experiences during World War II, and travels, including a trip to Los Angeles to visit Bette Davis on the set of the motion picture Elizabeth and Essex. The 1905 diary contains photographs of Woodward's school friends.
  - Diary 1 and Diary 2, 1905-1919 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Diary 3 and Diary 4, 1923-1948 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Diary 5 and Diary 6, 1939-1944 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Diary 7, 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Diary 8, 1949-1954 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Diary 9 and Diary 10, 1944-1958 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Diary 11 and Diary 12, 1959-1962 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Diary 13 and Diary 14, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Diary 15 and Diary 16, 1965-1968 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Diary 17, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Notes, Notebooks, and Writings, 1915-1969, Series 6:; (Boxes 5, 8; 21 folders)
  This series includes lists of art works, exhibition guest books, and miscellaneous writings by Woodward including drafts of his book Adventure in Marine Painting.
  - Notebook Listing Art Work, 1915-1931 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Lists of Art Work, 1933-1969, (2 folders; see also Box 8) (Box 5, Folder 5-6)
  - Exhibition Guest Book, 1948-1958 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Exhibition Guest Book, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Exhibition Guest Book, 1955-1964 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1933-1959, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 10-11)
  - Poems by Woodward, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Outline for Personal Memoirs Painting is My Life, undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Manuscript Twins, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Manuscript The American Soldier in the Pyrenees or an Artist on Leave, Undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Drafts for Book Adventure in Marine Painting, 1946, (4 folders) (Box 5, Folder 16-19)
  - Layout and Galley Proof for Book Adventure in Marine Painting, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Typescript Introductory Remarks to Gallery of Paintings, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Typescripts, undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Writings by Others, 1952, undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Oversized Lists of Art Work, 1938-1939 (Box 8 (sol))
- Business Records, 1924-1969, Series 7:; (Boxes 5-6; 15 folders)
  Business records include an auction catalog, account books for the sale of Woodward's book and art work, and miscellaneous receipts. Records of art classes taught by Woodward include lists of participants, accounts of fees paid, and printed advertisements.
  - Auction Catalog for the Library of Woodward's Father, Frank E. Woodward, 1924 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Account Book for the Sales of Book Adventure in Marine Painting, 1946-1948, (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 25-26)
  - Art Class Records, 1950-1953, undated, (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
  - Account Book for Book Sales, Art Work Sold, and Christmas List, 1956-1961 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Art-Related Receipts and Price Lists, 1932-1969, undated, (7 folders) (Box 6, Folder 4-10)
  - Receipts for Dues of Art-Related Organizations, 1937-1961 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Receipts, 1934-1966, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Scrapbook, 1875-1919, Series 8:; (Box 6; 1 folder)
  The scrapbook contains clippings and exhibition announcements and catalogs.
  - Scrapbook, 1875-1919 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Printed Material, 1916-1970, Series 9:; (Boxes 6-7; 0.75 linear feet)
  Printed material consists of clippings, copies of the U. S. Air Corps Magazine The Rip Chord for which Woodward did the cover illustrations, prospectuses, exhibition announcements and catalogs, reproductions of art work, a booklet, and brochures. Miscellaneous printed material includes reproductions of a photograph of Woodward's father, Frank E. Woodward, and a program for an event honoring Dr. T. Tertius Noble.
  - Clippings, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Clippings, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Clippings, 1920-1939 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Clippings, 1940-1949 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Clippings, 1950-1956 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Clippings, 1957-1959 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Clippings, 1960-1969 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Clippings, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - U. S. Air Corps Magazine The Rip Chord, 1943-1944, (5 folders) (Box 6, Folder 23-27)
  - Prospectuses for Art Exhibitions, 1932-1933, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Prospectuses for Art Exhibitions, 1934 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Prospectuses for Art Exhibitions, 1935-1936 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Prospectuses for Art Exhibitions, 1937, (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 31-32)
  - Prospectuses for Art Exhibitions, 1938, (3 folders) (Box 6, Folder 33-35)
  - Prospectuses for Art Exhibitions, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Prospectuses for Art Exhibitions, 1941-1947 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Prospectuses for Art Exhibitions, 1950-1954 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Prospectuses for Art Exhibitions, 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Prospectuses for Art Exhibitions, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Prospectuses for Art Exhibitions, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Prospectuses for Art Exhibitions, 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Prospectuses for Art Exhibitions, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Prospectuses for Art Exhibitions, 1964-1969 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1920-1929 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1933-1939 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1941-1948 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1954-1959 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1960-1962 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs, 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Exhibition Announcements and Catalogs for Others, 1958-1966, undated (Box 6, Folder 54)